Select A Image from Gallery
Draw lines to indicate best part of different Images
Select fast init for faster solution of Gradients
Use different metrices to choose regions in images
Note some metrices like match color & edge doesnt peform well
You can see which regions are selected for different images
Some metrices select more plausible regions
Some metrics produce worser results
Now we enter HD mode, where compuation is more expensive and consumes more time
MatchGradient is much slower but produce better results than MatchColor
If still not satified by the results, you can add more strokes or more image to guide the algorithm
The man in the middle is picked from new image
Now I'm playing with MatchColor. It takes much more strokes but still produces worser results than Match Gradients